Grace Hartigan Papers
Grace Hartigan Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - General correspondence-subject files
    - New York State, 1980; 1993,; 2000 (Box 22)
    - New York State Art Teachers Association, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
    - New York University (New York, New York), 1972; 1984 (Box 22)
    - The New Yorker, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Newport Harbor Art Museum (Newport Beach, California), 1983-1990 (Box 22)
    - Newsweek, 1959 (Box 22)
    - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
    - Northern Virginia Community College (Alexandria, Virginia), 1975 (Box 22)
    - O, 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Obel, Karen, 1987-1988; includes essay on GH (Box 22)
    - O'Connor, Francis V., 1970-1975; includes dissertation outline (Box 22)
    - O'Donnell, Petey, 1990-1992 (Box 22)
    - O'Hara, Frank, 1954-1983 (Box 22)
      See also Le Sueur, Joseph; Memorabilia: Photographs: Personal photographs: Grace Hartigan with others; Memorabilia: Photographs: Personal photographs: Photos of others
    - Oklahoma City Museum, 1969; 2002-2003 (Box 22)
    - Ollendorf Fine Arts (Long Island City, New York), 1975 (Box 22)
    - O'Neil, Martin, 1999-2001 (Box 22)
    - Ordeman, John, 1970-1989 (Box 22)
      See also St. Paul's Parish (Baltimore, Maryland)
    - Organization of Independent Artists, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Osaka International Festival Society, 1958 (Box 22)
    - Ostergaard, Gail, 1994-1998; undated (Box 22)
    - P, 1 folder (Box 22)
    - The Painter's Guild, 1987 (Box 22)
    - Pajak, Elizabeth (Betty), 1981-1993 (Box 22)
    - [Herbert B.] Palmer and Company (art dealer and collector, Los Angeles, California), 1982 (Box 22)
    - Palyjcuk, Wasyl, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Pan, Yihang, 1989-1998; includes hand-colored kiri-e piece (Japanese cut-paper work) (Box 22)
    - Parlato, John, 1978 (Box 22)
    - The Parrish Art Museum (Southampton, New York), 1998-2001 (Box 22)
    - Pavia, Philip, 1987; 1998,; 2003 (Box 22)
    - Pearson, Steve and Alicia, 1996-1998; undated (Box 22)
    - Pease, Roland, 1959-1964; undated (Box 22)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1970-1900; undated (Box 22)
    - Pensacola Museum of Art (Pensacola, Florida), 2003 (Box 22)
    - Perloff, Marjorie, 1975-1978; material regarding a book she was writing on Frank O'Hara (Box 22)
    - Perry, Beatrice, 1959-2000; 5 folders (Box 23)
    - Perry, Hart Jr., 1967-2003 (Box 23)
    - Pew, Elaine, 1996-1999; undated (Box 23)
    - Pfalzgalerie (Kaiserslautern, Germany), 1999-2000 (Box 23)
    - Philadelphia College of Art, 1982-1983 (Box 23)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Phillips, Gerry, 1985-1986; undated (Box 23)
    - Phillips, Paula, 1995-1998; undated (Box 23)
    - Pierce, Constance (Connie), 1976-1992 (Box 23)
    - Pipkin, Suzanne, 1976; 1979-1980 (Box 23)
    - Plansky, Carl, 1992-2000; undated (Box 23)
    - Polinske, Kenneth (Kenny), 1986-1987; undated (Box 23)
    - Ponselle, Rosa, 1981-1982; 2000 (Box 23)
    - Porter, Fairfield, 1954 (Box 23)
    - Portland Museum of Art (Portland, Maine), 1997-1999; includes letter from GH to director Daniel O'Leary (Box 23)
    - Portland School of Art (Portland, Maine), 1991 (Box 23)
    - Poston, Lewis, 1993-1995 (Box 23)
    - Price, Barbara, undated (Box 23)
    - Prioleau, Betsy, 1999-2003; undated (Box 23)
    - Project Rebuild (Udine, Italy), 1976 (Box 23)
    - Queens Museum of Art, 1997; 1999 (Box 23)
    - Quisgard, Liz, 1989 (Box 23)
    - R, 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Rabin, Ed, 1991; 1999 (Box 24)
    - Rabkin, Leo and Dorothy, 1958 (Box 24)
    - Raimondi, John, 1984-1997; undated (Box 24)
    - Rakusin, Sadie, 1975 (Box 24)
    - Rand, Archie and Maria, 1988-2003; undated; includes GH on "power" and "women artists' drawings" (Box 24)
    - Randolph-Macon Women's College, See Maier Museum of Art (Lynchburg, Virginia)
    - Random House, 1983 (Box 24)
    - Rango, Jo, 1980-1999; undated (Box 24)
    - Ratcliff, Carter, 1992-1995 (Box 24)
    - Ratliff, Floyd, 1992 (Box 24)
    - Redmond, Catherine, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
    - Reed College (Portland, Oregon), 1969; undated (Box 24)
    - The Reporter (New York, New York), 1959 (Box 24)
    - Republican Senatorial Inner Circle, 2001; includes GH comment on George W. Bush (Box 24)
    - Reuter, Barbara, 1973-1974; includes some biographical notes (Box 24)
    - Rhode Island School of Design (RISD) (Providence, RI), 1972-1976; 2002-2003 (Box 24)
    - Richardson, Brenda, 1990; 1997,; 1999 (Box 24)
    - Riley, Lee and Helen, 1983-2003; undated; includes letter from GH (Box 24)
    - Ringling Museum of Art (Sarasota, Florida), 1997 (Box 24)
    - Ritchell, Ann, 1970; 1974 (Box 24)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1953-1955; 1957; includes Rivers' statement about his artistic approach (Box 24)
    - Robert Keene Gallery (Southampton, New York), 1959 (Box 24)
    - Robert Miller Gallery (New York, New York), 1959; 2003 (Box 24)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1972; material re. "Salute to Charlie Chaplin" (Box 24)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1975 (Box 24)
    - Rockville Arts Place (Rockville, Maryland), 1992-1993 (Box 24)
    - Rogoff, Jay, 1988; 1993,; 1996 (Box 24)
    - Rolfes, Sidney and Maria, 1959; undated (Box 24)
    - Roll-preissler, Audrey, 1996 (Box 24)
    - Rood, Beverly, 1998-1999 (Box 24)
    - Rosa Esman Gallery (New York, New York), 1981-1982 (Box 24)
    - Rosapepe, Jim and Sheilah Kast, 2001 (Box 24)
    - Rosemont College (Rosemont, Pennsylvania), 1997-1998 (Box 24)
    - Rosenberg, Harold, 1966; 1973,; 1975 (Box 24)
    - Rosenfeld, Michael, See Michael Rosenfeld Gallery (New York, New York)
    - Rosenthal Art Slides, 1976 (Box 24)
    - [Mark] Rothko Foundation, 1971 (Box 24)
    - Rothman, Sidney, See Sidney Rothman Gallery (Barnegat Light, New Jersey)
    - Rutgers University (Camden, New Jersey), 1982-1997 (Box 24)
    - Ryan, Deborah, 1997-1999 (Box 24)
    - Ryerson, Charles, 1984; 1999 (Box 24)
    - S, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Sachs Gallery (New York, New York), 1976 (Box 25)
    - Sachs, Sid, 1995 (Box 25)
    - St. James Press (London, United Kingdom), 1975; 1982 (Box 25)
    - St. Louis Art Museum (St. Louis, Missouri), 1974; 1984 (Box 25)
    - St. Paul's Parish (Baltimore, Maryland), 1970 see also; 1980,; 1989 (Box 25)
      See Beaman, Dorothy; Ordeman, John
    - St. Paul's School (Brooklinville, Maryland), 1970; 1975 (Box 25)
    - Salant, Walter and Edna, 1962; 1964,; 1987 (Box 25)
    - Saler, Karen, 1965-1968; Additional material in Oversize box 1 (Box 25)
    - Salt, John, Jean, Thomas and Katy, 1972-2004; undated (Box 25)
    - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Sandler, Irving, 1977-1998; undated (Box 25)
    - Santa Fe Institute of Fine Arts (Santa Fe, New Mexico), 1984 (Box 25)
    - Santa Rosa Junior College (Santa Rosa, California), 1977; 1982 (Box 25)
    - Santiago, Richard and Maria, 1996-1997; undated (Box 25)
    - Sarah Campbell Blaffer Foundation, 1978 (Box 25)
    - Sawyer, Kenneth, 1957; 1960 (Box 25)
    - Schapiro, Miriam (Mimi) and Paul Brach, 1954; 1957,; 1980-1985,; undated (Box 25)
    - Schimmel, Yvonne, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Schneebaum, Tobias, 1988-2001 (Box 25)
    - Schneidt, May, 1977 (Box 25)
    - Scholastic Art & Writing Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 25)
    - Schrade, Art, 1999-2000; undated; includes letter from GH (Box 25)
    - Schutzenhofer, Josef, 1987; 1988,; undated (Box 25)
    - Schuyler, James, 1956; 1995,; 1997 (Box 25)
    - Schwarz, Joanna, 2000-2001; undated (Box 25)
    - Schweitzer, Albert (artist), 1994-2001; includes letter from GH, many handmade cards (Box 25)
    - Scott, Ce, 1997; undated (Box 26)
    - Scott, Sam, 1972-2001; undated (Box 26)
    - Segal, George, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Seldin, Jeff, 1974?-1977; undated (Box 26)
    - Seraphin Gallery (Philadephia, Pennsylvania), 2003 (Box 26)
    - Shamsky, Constance, 1971-1972 (Box 26)
    - Shapiro, Babe, 1995; undated (Box 26)
    - Shapolsky, Anita, See Anita Shapolsky Gallery (New York, New York)
    - Sherman, Peter and Winifred, 1993-2001 (Box 26)
    - Shiflett, Drew, 1979; 1981,; 1990 (Box 26)
    - Shore, Tony, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Siden, Franklin, See Franklin Siden Gallery (Detroit, Michigan)
    - Sidney Rothman Gallery (Barnegat Light, New Jersey), 1978 (Box 26)
    - Silva, Eliseo Art, 2001-2003 (Box 26)
    - Silver, Carole (sister-in-law of Walter Silver), 1998-2001 (Box 26)
    - Silver, Jonathan and Barbara, 1992; undated; includes GH notes for tribute (Box 26)
    - Silver, Walter, 1952-1994 (Box 26)
      See also Memorabilia: Photographs: Personal photographs: Photos of others
    - Simpson, Alan K. (Senator), 1992 (Box 26)
    - Skidmore College (Saratoga Springs, New York), 1970; 1984,; 1993,; 2000-2001 (Box 26)
    - Skold, Stacey, 1994-1996 (Box 26)
    - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture (Skowhegan, Maine), 1977-1995 (Box 26)
    - Slivka, David, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Smith, Alexander, 1977-1979; includes Frank O'Hara material ("Oranges" and "Meditation in an Emergency") (Box 26)
    - Smith, Arvie, 1999; undated; includes letter of recommendation from GH (Box 26)
    - Smith, David, 1959; undated (Box 26)
    - Smith, Hazel, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
    - Smithsonian Museum (Washington, D.C.), 1971-2000 (Box 26)
    - Soby, James Thrall, 1955-1962 (Box 26)
    - Solomon & Co., 1984 (Box 26)
    - Solomon, Holly, See Holly Solomon Gallery (New York, New York)
    - Somers, John and Marion, 1976-2001 (Box 26)
    - Sotheby's, 1981 (Box 26)
    - Southern Illinois University (Edwardsville, Illinois), 1969-1970; 1985 (Box 26)
    - Sparks, Esther, 1984; 1990,; 1991 (Box 26)
    - Sparks, John, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Spaventa, George, ca. 1968 (Box 26)
    - Springbok Editions, Inc. (New York, New York), 1969-1971 (Box 26)
    - Stam, Gera, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Stanton, Frank, 1965 (Box 26)
    - State University of New York College at Plattsburgh, 1977-1980 (Box 26)
    - State University of New York College at Purchase, 1981-1989 (Box 26)
    - States (Taylor), Sarah, 1978-1984; undated (Box 26)
    - Stefanelli, Joe, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
    - Steinbaum Krauss Gallery (New York, New York), 1996 (Box 27)
    - Stephan, Gary, 1994; includes GH letter of recommendation (Box 27)
    - Stevens, May, 1993; 2001 (Box 27)
    - Stevens, Rex, Regina and Ryan, 1986-2003; undated; 3 folders; Rex Stevens was GH's studio assistant; includes GH letter of recommendation (Box 27)
    - Stewart, Bill, 1975-1977 (Box 27)
    - Stiles, George, 1959 (Box 27)
    - Still, Patricia, 1980; 1990-1991; includes 2 letters from GH (Box 27)
    - Stolz, Joan, 1984-1990; undated (Box 27)
    - Straughan, Carolyn, 1976 (Box 27)
    - Stroffolino, Chris, 1988; 1997,; 1999 (Box 27)
    - Stroud, Marion Boulton ("Kippy"), See Fabric Workshop (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Style (magazine), 1996; 2002; includes letter from GH (Box 27)
    - Succhitani, Sandra and John, 1983-1985 (Box 27)
    - Sugatt, Mary, 1985 (Box 27)
    - Sujo, Clara Diament, See CDS Gallery (New York, New York)
    - Sullivan, Mark, 1988; includes GH letter of recommendation (Box 27)
    - Susquehanna Art Museum (Harrisburg, Pennsylvania), 1999-2000; undated; includes letter from GH and interview with GH (Box 27)
    - Swatch Co., 1994; includes letter from GH (Box 27)
    - Sweet Briar College (Sweet Briar, Virginia), 1991; 2001 (Box 27)
    - Syracuse University (Syracuse, New York), 1968-1969; 1974,; 1998 (Box 27)
    - T, 1 folder (Box 27)
    - Tabak, Maynatalie (Mrs. Harold Rosenberg), 1958-1979; includes original Steinberg drawing inscribed to her; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Tafel, Edgar, 1975; undated (Box 28)
    - Tarsell, Emily, 1979; undated (Box 28)
    - Taylor, Patrick, 1982; includes transcript of interview with GH (Box 28)
    - Tellez, Emily, 1998-2002; includes handmade cards (Box 28)
    - Tiber Press, undated (Box 28)
    - Tibor de Nagy Gallery (New York, New York), 1954; 1959-1960,; 1970,; 1980,; 1990,; 1994,; 2000; includes 2 GH tributes to TdN (Box 28)
      See also Myers, John Bernard
    - Tillim, Sidney, 1969-1970 (Box 28)
    - Tobey C. Moss Gallery (Los Angeles, California), 1999 (Box 28)
    - Toninelli, Romeo, See Galleria Minima (Milan)
    - Towson State University (Towson, Maryland), 1982-1983 (Box 28)
    - Trefuy, Frank, 1974; 1976 (Box 28)
    - Tumulty, Philip, 1973-1989 (Box 28)
    - Udine, Italy, See Project Rebuild (Udine, Italy)
    - Uhl, Barbara, 1974; undated (Box 28)
    - UNICEF, 1991 (Box 28)
    - United States Information Agency, 1971 (Box 28)
    - Universal Limited Art Editions, 1984-1985 (Box 28)
      See also Art Institute of Chicago; Grosman, Tatyana
    - University of Arizona, 1982 (Box 28)
    - University of Chicago, 1996 (Box 28)
    - University of Colorado at Boulder, 1980 (Box 28)
    - University of Connecticut at Storrs, 1982 (Box 28)
    - University of Delaware, 1974; 1981 (Box 28)
    - University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 1971 (Box 28)
    - University of Iowa, 1979 (Box 28)
    - University of Kansas, 1973; 1976,; 1994 (Box 28)
    - University of Maryland, College Park, 1979-1999; 2001 (Box 28)
    - University of Maryland (Baltimore County), 1995-1996 (Box 28)
    - University of Massachusetts (Amherst campus), 1976; 1997 (Box 28)
    - University of Michigan, 1992 (Box 28)
    - University of Minnesota (Minneapolis), 1963; 1983 (Box 28)
    - University of Minnesota (Duluth), 1977 (Box 28)
    - University of New Mexico, 1973-1995 (Box 28)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1982 (Box 28)
    - University of North Carolina (Greensboro), 1994-1995 (Box 28)
    - University of Rhode Island, 1994 (Box 28)
    - University of Texas at Austin, 1969-1986 (Box 28)
    - University of Washington, 1970 (Box 28)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1997 (Box 28)
    - University Publications of America, 1984-1985 (Box 28)
    - Upin, Ira, 1974; 1978,; 1986,; 1993,; 1996 (Box 28)
    - V, 1 folder (Box 28)
    - Van Ameringe, Judyth, 1985-1989 (Box 28)
    - Van Campen, Jerry, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
    - Van Devanter, Ann C., 1973 (Box 28)
    - Vanity Fair, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Vecchi, Floriano, 1989-1994; undated (Box 28)
      See also Castleman, Riva; Memorabilia: Photographs: Personal photographs: Grace Hartigan with others
    - Vereano, David, See Bradley, George
    - Vermont Studio Center (Johnson, Vermont), 1986-1998 (Box 29)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (Richmond, Virginia), 1973-1989 (Box 29)
    - Virginia and Henry (Box 29)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Art (Richmond, Virginia), 1969 (Box 29)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Blacksburg, Virginia), 1970-1977 (Box 29)
    - Visual Artists and Galleries Association, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Vivar, Monica, 1998 (Box 29)
    - Voell, ? (Dr.), 1980 (Box 29)
    - W, 1 folder (Box 29)
    - Walker, Walter ("Skip"), Zoe and Brianna, 1995-2001; undated; includes handmade cards, GH letters (Box 29)
    - Wallace, Pam, 1978-1985 (Box 29)
    - Wallace, Weldon, 1983 (Box 29)
    - Wanzung, Carl, 1976; undated (Box 29)
    - Washington University (St. Louis, Missouri), 1979-1980 (Box 29)
    - Washington Women's Art Center (Washington, D.C.), 1979 (Box 29)
    - Waters, John, undated (Box 29)
    - Weinberg and Green, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Weiner, Laura and Leslie, 1980-2003 (Box 29)
    - Weissman, David, 1996-2000; includes student papers (Box 29)
    - Weissman, Julian and Karen, 1983-2003; undated; includes comments on Martin Bush (Box 29)
    - Wellesley College Museums (Wellesley, Massachusetts), 1992-1998 (Box 29)
    - Westchester County Times (New Milford, Connecticut), undated (Box 29)
    - Wexner Center for the Arts (Columbus, Ohio), 1999-2000 (Box 29)
    - Whirlwind and Company (Women's Museum, New York), 2000 (Box 29)
    - The White House, 1982 (Box 29)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art (New York, New York), 1952-2000; 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Wichita Art Museum (Wichita, Kansas), 1996; 1999 (Box 30)
    - Wichita State University (Wichita, Kansas), 1992 (Box 30)
    - Widdows, Bruce, 1992-1994 (Box 30)
    - Wiener, Phyllis Ames, 1983 (Box 30)
    - Wilcox, Darrell, 1997-1998; undated (Box 30)
    - Williams, Betty, 1979-2001 (Box 30)
    - Wilson, Debra, 1999-2001 (Box 30)
    - Wires, Susan, undated (Box 30)
    - Withers, Josephine, 1978-1981; undated; includes many photos from filming of documentary on GH (Box 30)
    - Wittels, Dan, 1979-1983 (Box 30)
    - Wodzianski, Andrew, 2000-2003 (Box 30)
    - Woelffer, Emerson, 1992 (Box 30)
    - Woffard, Philip, 1988 (Box 30)
    - Wolman, Elsa, 1981; includes handmade necktie (Box 30)
    - Women's Art Registry of Minnesota (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1983 (Box 30)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, 1986-1987; 1995,; undated (Box 30)
    - Woodmere Art Museum (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1994; 1999 (Box 30)
    - Woodward Foundation, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Worcester Art Museum (Worcester, Massachusetts), 1984-2001 (Box 30)
    - Wun, Clifford, 1994; undated (Box 30)
    - Xenakis, Tom, 1998-2003 (Box 30)
    - Y, 1 folder (Box 30)
    - Yaddo (Saratoga Springs, New York), 1951 (Box 30)
    - Yale University (New Haven, Connecticut), 1987 (Box 30)
    - "Yoryi", 1977-1993; undated; includes three letters from GH (Box 30)
    - Young, Charles, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Yunkers, Adja, 1975 (Box 30)
    - Z, 1 folder (Box 30)
    - Zeller (Patricks), Ruth, undated (Box 30)
    - Zierler, William, 1970-1981 (Box 30)
  - Unidentified
    - A-L (Box 31)
    - M-Z (Box 31)
    - Unidentified (Box 31)
- Writings
  - Addresses and remarks, 1990; 1995,; undated (Box 31)
  - Autobiographical material
    - Excerpts from correspondence-subject files, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Journal excerpts (Box 31)
    - Prepared for publication (Box 31)
  - Journals, 1951-1955; includes transcript of 1954 journal; 7 folders (Box 32)
  - "Living for Art: The New York Art Scene in the 'Fifties: The diaries of Grace Hartigan and Photographs of Walter Silver" typescript, 1951-1955; contains GH's diary entries only; there are none of Silver's photographs and although the cover sheet says "introduction by Robert Mattison" that too is not present (Box 32)
    For additional Robert Mattison material, see also General correspondence-subject files: Mattison, Robert Saltonstall
  - Miscellaneous, fragments, poem, photocopy of inscribed photograph (Box 32)
- Memorabilia
  - Biographical Material (Box 32)
  - Calendar (extensively annotated), 1950 (Box 32)
  - Financial (Box 32)
  - Medical (Box 32)
  - Painting lists (Box 32)
  - PBS special, "American Masters: Jackson Pollock", hartigan_001; inclues interview with Grace Hartigan; 1 VHS cassette (Box 32)
  - Photographs
    - Art photographs
      - Works by Grace Hartigan, 1950-1989; undated; Additional material in Oversize box 1 (Box 39)
      - Studio Shots, 1944-1969; undated; Additional material in Oversize box 1 (Box 40)
      - Multiple works by Grace Hartigan, undated; Additional material in Oversize box 1 (Box 41)
      - Works by others (de Kooning, unknown) (Box 41)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959; 1997,; 1999,; undated (Box 41)
    - Negatives and transparencies (Box 33)
      Walter Silver negatives
      "Anatomy of Calvert Street" 1969
      Art History Lecture
      "Fire and Water" 1969
      "Great Queens Series"
      Unidentified 1969
    - Personal photographs
      - Grace Hartigan, 1942-1959; 1987,; 1989,; 1993,; undated; Additional material in Oversize box 1 (Box 42)
      - Grace Hartigan with others, 1942-1959; undated; Additional material in Oversize box 1 (Box 43)
      - Photos of others, 1945-1980; undated; Additional material in Oversize box 1 (Box 43)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Oversize 1)
    - Miscellany (Box 32)
  - Printed material
    - Articles, 1950-2003; undated; 6 folders (Box 34)
    - Clippings
      - Clippings, 1950-1985; 7 folders (Box 35)
      - Clippings, 1986-2002; undated; 6 folders (Box 36)
    - Discussion panel programs, 1955; undated (1950s) (Box 36)
    - Exhibition catalogs
      - Solo shows, 1951-2006; 5 folders (Box 36)
      - Group shows, 1950-2003; 6 folders (Box 37)
      - Other artists (Box 37)
    - Theater and concert programs (Box 38)
    - Travel related (Box 38)